Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  - Accession A98-36
    - Worship Services/Liturgies, 1975-1984 (Box 89)
    - Service of Worship for All Persons, 1975-1976 (Box 89)
    - Candle [newsletter], 1977-1980 (Box 89)
    - Sojourner Helpers, 1978-1980 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner: Miscellaneous ideas, info., help, 1977-1984, undated (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1975-1977 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1977-1978, 1993 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1979-1982 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1982-1983 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1984 Oct., Dec. (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1985 April, Dec. (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1986 (Box 89)
    - The Sojourner [newsletter], 1987 (Box 89)
    - Inclusive Worship Project (Box 89)
    - Sexual Harassment: N.O.W. Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1982 (Box 89)
    - Pastoral Care and Dual Career Marriages, 1983 (Box 89)
    - Film and Media Resources, 1983 (Box 89)
    - Worship Services and Music, 1982-1983 (Box 89)
    - Retreat Resources, 1985 (Box 89)
    - Mary in the Hands of Her Sisters: God, the Church or Woman? by Melanie Reuter, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 89)
    - Loss of the Father God: Why Women Rage and Grieve, 1981 (Box 89)
    - Inclusive Eucharist Celebration, 1986 (Box 89)
    - Brown Bag Lunches, 1987-1988 (Box 89)
    - Marie Fortune, 1987-1988 (Box 89)
    - The Between Times [newsletter], 1986-1988 (Box 89)
    - Coordinator Applications, 1988-1990 (Box 89)
    - Women's Center Events, 1984-1991 (Box 89)
    - Slides: You are the Branches, 1979 (Box 89)
    - Slides: Women in the Ministry, 1976-1977 (Box 89)
    - Sub-Committee on Inclusive Languages, undated (Box 89)
    - Wesley Foundation Campus Ministry Songbook, 1975 (Box 89)
    - Role Plays, Liturgies, etc., 1977, undated (Box 89)
    - Daughters of Sarah, 1993-1995 (Box 89)
    - Grail Prayer Book, 1975 (Box 89)
    - Lifestyles, 1976 (Box 89)
    - Printed Material, 1993, undated (Box 89)
    - Printed Material on Women and Psychology, 1972 (Box 89)
    - Women: A Perspectives on a Movement, publication and audiocassette, 1973 (Box 89)
    - Printed Material: Joy in Singing, Sisters and Brothers Sing, The Words We Sing, 1977-1984 (Box 89)
    - United Methodist Clergy Women's Consultation, 1983 (Box 89)
    - From Hierarchy to Equality, 1978 (Box 90)
    - Herstory, 1972 (Box 90)
    - Sing a Woman Song, 1975 (Box 90)
    - Sexual Harassment in the UMC, 1990 (Box 90)
  - Accession A98-41
    - Atlantic Christian - Duke, 1987-1988 (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - Anglican Statements on the Church, undated (Box 90)
    - Baptist House of Studies, 1988-1993 (5 folders) (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Dec. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Jan.-Feb. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1995 March (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1995 April (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1995 May (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1995 June (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Jul.-Sept. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Nov. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Oct. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1994 May-Jun. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1994 April (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Jan. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1990 Jan. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Dec. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Nov. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Oct. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Sept. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Aug. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Jul. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Jun. (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Jan.-March (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Correspondence to Faculty, 1988-1992 (Box 91)
    - Committee on Ecumenical Perspectives and Interreligious Dialogue in Theological Education, 1988-1990 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Consultation on Ecumenical Perspectives and Interreligious Dialogue in Theological Education Meeting - Madison, WI. 1990 (Box 91)
    - Episcopal Studies, 1990-1993 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - General committee on Christian Unity and Interreligious Concerns, 1990-1991 (Box 91)
    - GCCUIC Quarterly Review Correspondence, 1991 (Box 91)
    - GCCUIC Meeting - Stony Point, NY, 1990 (Box 91)
    - GCCUIC General, 1989-90 (Box 91)
    - GCCUIC General, 1988-1992 (Box 91)
    - GCCUIC Annual Meeting - Nashville, TN. 1991 (Box 91)
    - North Carolina United Methodist Episcopal Dialogue, 1991-1993 (3 folders) (Box 91)
    - Presbyterian Studies, 1989-1992 (Box 91)
    - Richey, Russell E. - General, 1990-1991 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Richey, Russell E. - General, 1991-1992 (Box 91)
    - Survey of Seminaries and Ecumenism, 1988 (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Yahara Meeting - Minneapolis, MN. 1989-1990 (Box 91)
  - Accession A99-53
    - AAR/SBL Meetings, 1994-1996 (Box 91)
    - Association for Clinical Pastoral Education, 1987-1990 (Box 91)
    - A - Misc., 1991-1997 (Box 92)
    - Conway, Arkansas, 1996 (Box 92)
    - Arnold, Duane W.H. 1994 (Box 92)
    - Artspace, 1995 (Box 92)
    - Aspen Institute - Eastern Shore, M.D. 1994 (Box 92)
    - Brenneman, Sandy, 1996 (Box 92)
    - B - Misc., Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 92)
    - C - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Canterbury Cathedral Trust, 1991-1997 (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Canterbury - Visit of Dean John Simpson, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Canterbury, England, 1994-1996 (Box 92)
    - Canterbury Course, 1995-1996 (Box 92)
    - Canterbury Course, 1994 (Box 92)
    - Canterbury Course, 1993 (Box 92)
    - Canterbury Cathedral Board of Trustees - Visit, 1993 (Box 92)
    - Dean John Simpson of Canterbury School, 1989-1995 (Box 92)
    - Center for Living, 1997 (Box 92)
    - Cherry, Conrad, 1995-1996 (Box 92)
    - Cole, Darrell, 1995-1996 (Box 92)
    - General Conference - Candidates for the Episcopacy (Box 92)
    - Conference and SEJ conference Delegates, 1995-1996 (Box 92)
    - Congregational Development - UNC, 1994 (Box 92)
    - Connolly, Phillip, 1994-1995 (Box 92)
    - Cooper, David K. AIA, 1995 (Box 92)
    - The Catholic University of America, 1997 (Box 92)
    - Catholic Student Center, 1994 (Box 92)
    - Durham Congregations in Action (DCIA), 1988-1991 (Box 92)
    - Diaconal Ministry, 1989-1994 (Box 92)
    - Dyba, Christopher, 1998 (Box 92)
    - D - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 92)
    - Raleigh Lay Rally - Edenton St. UMC., 1991-1992 (Box 92)
    - Edgerton, N. Edward, 1940, 1987-1995 (Box 92)
    - Educational Opportunities, 1992-1994 (Box 92)
    - Elders Lay Participation in Ordination, undated (Box 92)
    - Electronic Keyboard, 1989 (Box 92)
    - Episcopal Studies, 1996 (Box 92)
    - Episcopal Church Foundation, 1995 (Box 92)
    - Triangle Ethics Initiative, 1998 (Box 92)
    - NCSU - Ethics in the Profession, 1987-1995 (Box 92)
    - E - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Miami, FL., Visit, 1996 (Box 92)
    - F - Misc Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 92)
    - G - Misc Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Globalization, 1988-1989 (Box 92)
    - Glover-Wetherington, Miriam Anne, 1991-1996 (Box 92)
    - Gomes, Peter, 1995-1997 (Box 92)
    - H - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Haggai Institute, 1993-1995 (Box 92)
    - Haire, E. R. Jr., 1996 (Box 92)
    - Heinke, Gary D., 1995-1996 (Box 92)
    - Hooker, Morna, 1993 (Box 92)
    - Installation Services, 1988-1995 (Box 92)
    - Islam Study (Pew Trust), 1991 (Box 92)
    - I - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 92)
    - Jenkins, David Oli, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Johnson, Luke, 1991 (Box 92)
    - Jones, Donald L. and Kevin Scott, 1994 (Box 92)
    - The Michael Jordan Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 92)
    - J - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Kajese, Kngston (Africa), 1997 (Box 92)
    - K - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 92)
    - Leadership Letters, 1995-1996 (Box 93)
    - Lee, Ronda, 1992 (Box 93)
    - Lewis, Douglas, 1985-1994 (Box 93)
    - Lord Corporation, 1997 (Box 93)
    - Lovin, Robin W., 1994-1996 (Box 93)
    - Lytle, Guy - Visit, 1996-1997 (Box 93)
    - M - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - Maquiban, Tim, 1994-1996 (Box 93)
    - Martin, Erin, 1994-1996 (Box 93)
    - Miller, Jerry, 1988 (Box 93)
    - Metcalfe, Jerry Lynn, 1994 (Box 93)
    - Minority Faculty Vita Bank, 1986 (Box 93)
    - Moltmann, Jurgen, 1985-1994 (Box 93)
    - Mini-Internship Program, 1994-1995 (Box 93)
    - Mc - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 93)
    - N - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 93)
    - O - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 93)
    - Oden, Thomas C., 1991 (Box 93)
    - Orthodox-Methodist Meeting, 1993-1995 (Box 93)
    - Oxford Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 93)
    - Palmer, Ruth, 1995 (Box 93)
    - Pan-Methodist Campaign for Children in Poverty, 1999 (Box 93)
    - Parish Ministry Fund, 1986 (Box 93)
    - P - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 93)
    - Parsonage Counseling Center, 1993 (Box 93)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1984-1983 (Box 93)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1995 (Box 93)
    - Phillips, Edward, 1996 (Box 93)
    - Pinsky, Mark, 1995-1997 (Box 93)
    - Pitts, Noah, O., Jr., 1986-1996 (Box 93)
    - Piwang, George, 1994-1996 (Box 93)
    - Presbyterian Studies, 1989-1991 (Box 93)
    - Proctor, Samuel, 1992-1995 (Box 93)
    - Providence UMC, Charlotte, NC., 1994-1995 (Box 93)
    - R - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 93)
    - Ream, Todd, 1996 (Box 93)
    - Retirement of Tenured Professors Before Age 70, 1985 (Box 93)
    - Rhodes College, Memphis, TN., 1996-1997 (Box 93)
    - Riddle, J.P., 1987-1988 (Box 93)
    - Richardson, Neville - Visit, 1985-1994 (Box 93)
    - Roberts, Bruce, 1995-1996 (Box 93)
    - Rudy, Kathy, 1992-1996 (Box 93)
    - Rutherfordton, NC - Frist U.M.C., 1991-1992 (Box 93)
    - S - Misc., Correspondence, 1994-1997 (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - St. John's House, 1989 (Box 93)
    - Sanford District Workshop, 1996-1997 (Box 93)
    - Schaller, Lyle, 1989-1995 (Box 93)
    - Scholarship Letters, 1985 (Box 93)
    - Seattle Pacific University, 1996 (Box 93)
    - Smith, Harry E., 1994-1995 (Box 93)
    - S.C. School of Ministry, 1994 (Box 93)
    - Snyder, George, 1986-1997 (Box 93)
    - Spanish Study, 1996 (Box 93)
    - Spartanburg Annual Conference, 1994 (Box 93)
    - Spectracom - Paul Schappaugh and Mike Reed, 1996 (Box 93)
    - Spencer, Jon Michael, 1993 (Box 93)
    - Stacey, David and Morna Hooker, 1985-1992 (Box 93)
    - Stallsworth, Paul T., 1992-1995 (Box 93)
    - Steinfels, Peter, 1993 (Box 93)
    - Styers, Randall, 1996 (Box 93)
    - T - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 93)
    - Turner, Linda Lyon, 1986 (Box 93)
    - Tyson, John H., 1992-1996 (Box 93)
    - U.M. Publishing House, 1994-1996 (Box 93)
    - U - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 93)
    - Vienna, Austria, 1991-1994 (Box 93)
    - Vosloo Visit, 1997-1998 (Box 93)
    - W - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - Weber, Helen, 1992-1997 (Box 93)
    - Wesley Men Banquet, 1992-1996 (Box 93)
    - Wilkes, Paul - Visit, 1994 (Box 93)
    - Worship and Sacred Space, 1993 (Box 93)
    - Y - Misc. Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 93)
    - Zhang, Jinglong, 1995-1996 (Box 93)
  - Accession A99-58
    - Academic Council, 1995-1996 (Box 94)
    - Admissions Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 94)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1993-1996 (Box 94)
    - Anlyan, William G. 1987-1993 (Box 94)
    - Annual Fund, 1982-1993 (Box 94)
    - Ascher, William, 1996 (Box 94)
    - Buehler, Al, 1985-1989 (Box 94)
    - Beckum, Leonard, 1989-1995 (Box 94)
    - Bulletin of Information for Prospective Students, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
    - Burness, John, 1990-1995 (Box 94)
    - Counseling and Psychological Services, 1984-1994 (Box 94)
    - Bryan Memorial Service, 1996 (Box 94)
    - Centurions, 1988-1992 (Box 94)
    - University Capital Campaign, 1989-1991 (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Conference on Career Choices, 1989-1994 (Box 94)
    - Center for Study of Aging and Human Development, 1993-1994 (Box 94)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1990-1995 (Box 94)
    - Commencement, 1993-1994 (Box 94)
    - Dean's Retreat, 1991-1995 (Box 94)
    - University Development, 1993-1996 (Box 94)
    - Dickerson, Janet Smith, 1994 (Box 94)
    - Distinguished Professorships, 1985-1993 (Box 94)
    - Dowell, Earl, 1994-1995 (Box 94)
    - Duke University Chapel, 1994-1996 (Box 94)
    - Duke Endowment Visit, 1995 (Box 94)
    - Duke Endowment Visit, 1996 (Box 94)
    - Duke Faculty/Employees: Miscellaneous, 1986-1995 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Evaluation Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Commons, 1987-1993 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Compensation, 1987-1993 (Box 94)
    - Faculty by Rank and Sex, 1990 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Nomenclature, 1991 (Box 94)
    - Employment Contracts, 1991-1993 (Box 94)
    - Fleishman, Joel, 1993 (Box 94)
    - Football Game and Cabinets Luncheon, 1994 (Box 94)
    - Final Materials on Formula Budget Preparations, 1988-1992 (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Founders Society Dinner, 1991-1995 (Box 94)
    - Gann, Dean Pamela, 1991-1992 (Box 94)
    - Gifts, 1991-1992 (Box 94)
    - Graduate Executive Meetings, 1991-1995 (Box 94)
    - Opening Convocation for Graduate and Professional Students, 1997 (Box 94)
    - Haltom, Allison (University Secretary), 1991-1995 (Box 94)
    - Harassment Policy, 1993-1995 (Box 94)
    - Homosexuality: Benefits, 1994-1995 (Box 94)
    - Housing for Ministries, 1989-1991 (Box 94)
    - President's Program for Human Resource Effectiveness, 1989-1993 (Box 94)
    - Incentive Formulas, 1989-1990 (Box 94)
    - Instrumentation Fund, 1988 (Box 94)
    - Internationals: Professors and Students, 1986-1994 (Box 94)
    - Internationalization, 1993-1994 (Box 94)
    - International Affairs, 1995-1996 (Box 94)
    - International Studies, 1988-1994 (Box 94)
    - Investments, 1987-1991 (Box 94)
    - Japan Initiative, 1991 (Box 94)
    - Center for Judaic Studies, 1992 (Box 94)
    - Kahr, Toby, 1989-1993 (Box 94)
    - Keller, Tom, 1991-1996 (Box 94)
    - Breakfast with Keohane, 1994 (Box 94)
    - Kenan Program in Ethics, 1995-1996 (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Kenan Ethics Committee, 1996 (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - Association of American Universities, 1988 (Box 95)
    - American Theological Society, 1995-1997 (Box 95)
    - American Theological Society, 1994-1995 (Box 95)
    - Association of Theological Schools, 1995-1996 (Box 95)
    - Association of Theological Schools, 1990-1996 (Box 95)
    - AUMTS, 1994-1995 (Box 95)
    - AUMTS: African Initiative Brief, 1986 (Box 95)
    - AUMTS: Dallas, 1995 (Box 95)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 95)
    - Board of Global Ministries, 1984-1988 (Box 95)
    - Board of Higher Education Annual Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 95)
    - Board of Higher Education and Ministry, 1995 (Box 95)
    - Board of Higher Education and Ministry Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 95)
    - Board of Higher Education and Ministry, 1994-1995 (Box 95)
    - Board of Ordained Ministry Interviews, 1986-1988 (Box 95)
    - Board of Ordained Ministry Chairs, 1994-1996 (Box 95)
    - Commission on Archives and History, 1986, 1993 (Box 95)
    - Commission on Religion and Race, 1992-1995 (Box 95)
    - Commission on the Status and Race of Women, 1985-1991 (Box 95)
    - Commission to Study the Ministry: Questionnaire for Bishops, 1989 (Box 95)
    - Dempster Graduate Fellowships, 1990-1996 (Box 95)
    - Diaconal Ministry, 1990-1995 (Box 95)
    - Women Full-Time Faculty, 1991 (Box 95)
    - Worship Committee, 1985-1996 (Box 95)
    - General Commission on Finance and Administration, 1993-1995 (Box 95)
    - General Conference, 1996 (Box 95)
    - General Council on Ministries, 1993-1994 (Box 95)
    - Harnish, John E., 1993-1997 (Box 95)
    - Lagree, Kevin, 1992 (Box 95)
    - Methodist Foundation, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Ministerial Education Fund (MEF) Scholarship Committee, 1986 (Box 95)
    - MEF Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 95)
    - Minds System, 1989-1994 (Box 95)
    - National Association of Schools and Colleges of the United Methodist Church, 1986-1994 (Box 95)
    - National Council of Churches, 1993-1995 (Box 95)
    - Russia Project, 1992-1995 (Box 95)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference: Lake Junaluska, 1996 (Box 95)
    - Seminary Relations, 1996 (Box 95)
    - Treese, Donald, 1993 (Box 95)
    - United Methodist Student Movement, 1996 (Box 95)
    - United Methodist Seminaries, 1991 (Box 95)
    - United Methodist Church Agencies, 1988 (Box 95)
    - University Theological School Dean's Meeting, 1996 (Box 95)
    - Western N.C. Reception, 1992-1995 (Box 95)
    - Western N.C. Conference Luncheon, 1996 (Box 95)
    - World Methodist Council, 1988 (Box 95)
    - University Senate, Arlington, VA, 1995 (Box 95)
    - United Methodist Polity Seminar, 1997 (Box 95)
    - Women Administrators and Faculty of United Methodist Theological Schools, 1992 (Box 95)
    - World Council of Churches: Canberra, Australia, 1991-1992 (Box 95)
  - Accession A2000-9
    - THE INDEPENDENT, 1994 Dec. 14 (Box 95)
  - Accession A2001-56
    - Divinity School Purpose and Profile Notebook, circa 1979 (Box 95)
    - Documents Relative to Divinity School Governance, 1962-1971 (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - Duke Circuit Rider, 1952 (Box 95)
    - Duke Circuit Rider, 1953 (Box 95)
    - Duke Circuit Rider, 1955 (Box 95)
    - Duke Circuit Rider, 1956 (Box 96)
    - Duke Circuit Rider, 1957 (Box 96)
  - Accession A2003-17
    - Admissions Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes and Other Business, 1981-1983 (Box 96)
    - Student Enrollment, 1980-1983 (Box 96)
    - Duke-Bonn Exchange: Student Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 96)
    - Duke-Bonn: Fall Semester, 1996 (Box 96)
    - Duke-Bonn Program, 1983, undated (Box 96)
    - Duke-Bonn Exchange: Papers, 1995-1996 (3 folders) (Box 96)
    - Duke-Bonn Exchange, 1997 (Box 96)
    - Sermon in German, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Accession A2003-34
    - Office of External Relations, 2000 (Box 96)
    - Office of External Relations, 2001 (Box 96)
    - Office of External Relations, 2002 (Box 96)
    - Office of External Relations, 2003 (Box 96)
  - Accession A2005-0031
    - Faculty Minutes, 1926 Sept. 18-1930 May 30 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1930 Sept. 24-1934 Jan. 10 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1934 Jan. 17-1936 June 4 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1936 Sept. 16-1941 May 29 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1941 Sept. 19-1943 May 21 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1943 Sept. 14-1944 Sept. 20 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1944 Sept. 22-1945 May 29 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1945 Sept. 21-1946 Oct. 9 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1946 Nov. 13-1947 May 30 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1947 Sept. 17-1948 June 4 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1948 Sept. 16-1949 Feb. 16 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1949 Mar. 8-1949 June 2 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1949 Sept. 27-1951 June 1 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1951 Sept. 17-1952 Jan. 30 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1952 Mar. 5-1952 Oct. 8 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1952 Nov. 5-1953 May 29 (Box 96)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1953 Sept. 14-1954 Sept. 14 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1954 Sept. 20-1955 Oct. 5 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1955 Nov. 5-1956 June 1 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1956 Sept. 17-1957 March 13 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1957 May 31-1958 May 30 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1958 Sept. 15-1959 June 5 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1959 Sept. 14-1960 Sept. 14 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1960 Sept. 19-1962 June 1 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1962 Sept. 17-1963 May 31 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1963 Sept. 16-1964 May 29 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1969 Sept.-1970 May 11 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1970 May29-1970 Sept. 16 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1970 Oct. 12-1971 May 3 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1971 May 12-1971 June 4 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1971 Sept. 7-1972 Sept. 11 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1972 Sept. 22-1974 May 9 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1979 Jan.11-1981 May 7 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1981 Sept. 1-1983 May 4 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1983 Aug. 29-1986 May 1 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1986 Sept. 3-1988 May 12 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1987 Mar. 2-1990 May 17 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1988 Sept. 1-1990 May 10 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1990 Sept. 1-1992 May 14 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1990 Aug. 25-1993 Mar. 30 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1992 Sept. 15-1994 Apr. 11 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1994 Sept. 1-1995 May 12 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1994 Sept. 12-1995 May 20 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1995 Sept. 1-1997 May 15 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1995 Oct. 4-1997 Jan. 30 (Box 97)
    - Faculty Minutes: Photograph filed with, circa 1995-1997 (Box 97)
    - Educational Affairs Council: Minutes, 1969-1972 (Box 97)
    - Educational Affairs Council: Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 97)
    - Educational Affairs Council: Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 97)
    - Educational Affairs Council: Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 97)
  - Accession A2006-0008
    - Frank Baker, 1990-1999 (Box 98)
    - W. D. Davies, 1998-2002 (Box 98)
    - Donn Michael Farris, 1992, 2005 (Box 98)
    - Thomas A. Langford, 1973, undated (Box 98)
    - Father Roland E. Murphy, 2000, 2002 (Box 98)
    - M. Wilson Nesbitt, 2003 (Box 98)
    - McMurry S. Richey, 1983-1996, 2005 (Box 98)
  - School of Religion Files
    Subseries scope/content note.
    - General Correspondence: Applications for Employment, Letters of Recommendation, 1925 (Box 98)
    - Formal Opening of the School, 1926 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: Faculty Appointments, Formal Opening Invitations, 1926 (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - Hymnan Material, Magazine Articles, 1927 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: Applications for Positions, 1927-1928 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: Applications for Positions, 1928-1929 (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 Jan.-March (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 April-May (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 June-July (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 Aug.-Sept. (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 Oct. (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 Nov. (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence, 1929 Dec. (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: A, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: B, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: C, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: D-E, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: F-G, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: H-I, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: J-K, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: L, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: M, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: N-R, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: S, 1930 (2 folders) (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: T, 1930 (Box 98)
    - General Correspondence: U-W, 1930 (Box 99)
    - General Correspondence: W-Z, 1930 (Box 99)
    - Data in Statistical Tables of Seminaries, 1931 (Box 99)
    - Extension Work, 1931 (Box 99)
    - National Association of Bible Instructors, 1931 (Box 99)
    - Reports of the School of Religion, 1926-1931 (Box 99)
    - General Correspondence, 1931 Jan. (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - General Correspondence, 1931 Feb. (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - General Correspondence, 1931 March (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - General Correspondence, 1931 April (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - General Correspondence, 1931 May (3 folders) (Box 99)